greendotonline.com 2006-11-05

# Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy is provided by Green Dot Corporation (“GDC”)  
(Effective November 15, 2004)**

GDC values your trust and respects your expectation of privacy. As such, we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of your personal financial information. This document outlines our privacy policy in connection with the nonpublic personal information we receive regarding you.

Green Dot Corporation is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the sites [http://www.GreenDotOnline.com](http://www.greendotonline.com/) (Collectively and individually referred to as “this web site”). Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact GDC’s Privacy Officer by emailing Privacy@greendotcorp.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at [ http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

**Visitors to Our Web Site.**  Visitors to our web site remain anonymous, unless they register for a service or otherwise elect to disclose their identity to us. Although we do not collect personally identifying information about persons who simply visit our site, we do collect certain limited information about visitors, such as their IP address (a numeric address assigned automatically to computers when they access the Internet). We also attempt to place “cookies” on a computer to track a visitor’s use of our web site. A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on your hard drive. It takes up very little room on your system and helps us to customize our site and make its navigation easier for you. We sometimes use cookies to help estimate the number of visitors to our site and to determine which areas are the most popular. Unless you register with us for a service, the cookie does not provide us with any personally identifying information about you, such as your name or address.

**Our Collection and Use of Information About You.**  We collect nonpublic personal information about you in order to understand your needs, administer our business, process your transactions, and provide you with products and services. We obtain nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

Information you provide to us by telephone, on applications, in membership requests, through this web site, and on other forms (such as your name, address, telephone number and date of birth);

Information about your transactions with us, joint marketers, or others (such as your card balance, payment history, parties to transactions, and card usage); and 

Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency (such as your creditworthiness and credit history).

**Our Disclosure of Information.**  We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements, such as insurance agents and card issuers, so that they can market goods and services to you. We also may disclose:

Some of this information, such as your name and address, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf (e.g., to companies that assist us with mailings).

Information about your card, membership, and transactions: (a) where it is necessary or helpful to effect, process or confirm your membership and transactions; (b) to verify the existence and availability of funds associated with your card; (c) to comply with legal process, such as subpoenas and court orders; (d) to law enforcement authorities if we believe a crime has been committed; and (e) if you give us your consent.

We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about our current or former customers to unaffiliated third parties except as set forth in this policy or as permitted by law.

**Additional Cardholders.**  Should you decide to purchase an additional card, we will ask you information about the additional cardholder, such as that person’s name and relationship to you. Additionally, that person's use of the card will be subject to the terms of the cardholder agreement.

**Use of Agents.**  We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

**Use of Service Providers.**  We use other third parties to provide statistical tracking and advertising effectiveness for our web site. When you sign up for GDC services, we may share information such as your name and address and other information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

**Information Security.**  We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to our employees who have a need to know such information (e.g., to process your transactions). We train our employees on the importance of customer privacy and confidentiality. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard the nonpublic personal information of our customers.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such your social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

**Links to Other Web Sites.**  Our web site may feature links to third party web sites that offer goods, services or information. Some of these sites may appear as windows-within-windows at our web site. When you click on one of these links, you will be leaving our site and will no longer be subject to this policy. We are not responsible for the information collection practices of the other web sites that you visit and urge you to review their privacy policies before you provide them with any personally identifiable information. Third party sites may collect and use information about you in a way that is different from this policy.

**Other Privacy Rights.**  You may have other privacy protections under some state laws. We will comply with applicable state laws regarding information about you. For example, certain state laws may restrict the types of information we may disclose about you or require us to provide you with additional notices or opt-out rights.

**Information for Vermont Residents.**  In accordance with Vermont regulations, we will not disclose nonpublic personal financial information about you while you remain a resident of Vermont to nonaffiliated third parties (other than as permitted by law) unless you authorize us to make that disclosure. Your authorization must be in writing or, if you agree, in electronic form. If we disclose information about you to nonaffiliated third parties with whom we have joint marketing agreements, we will only share information about your name, contact information, and our own transactions and experiences with you.

**Maintaining Accurate Information.**  We have a process in place that helps us to maintain the accuracy of the personally identifiable information that we collect. Please visit our web site at [http://www.GreenDotOnline.com](http://www.greendotonline.com/) to review and correct information about yourself, such as a change in your name, address or e-mail address. If you believe that our information is inaccurate or incomplete, you also can contact us at the number or address listed below and ask us to correct or update our information.

**Changes to this Policy.**  We may add to, delete from, or otherwise change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a notice of the change (or an amended Privacy Policy) at this website. If required by law, we will send you a notice of the change by a method that we select and that complies with applicable state and federal laws as well as the terms of your cardholder agreement. Such methods could include email, postal mail and/or posting on this website. Your continued use of our web site or any service following such notification will constitute evidence of your agreement to the revised Policy.

**Communications from our Web Site.**  We will occasionally send you information on new products, features or promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section below.

In addition, we may also send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may opt-out of these communications. Please see “Choice and Opt-out” section below.

**Choice/Opt-out**

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain marketing and promotional activities, when we ask for this information. For example, when you signup for a product or service from us, you can opt-out of these communications.

If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by calling us at (877) 434-3578 or writing to us at Green Dot Customer Service, P.O. Box 1187, Monrovia, California 91017.

**Questions.**  If you have any questions regarding this Policy, you can email us at [Privacy@greendotcorp.com ](mailto:Privacy@greendotcorp.com) or call us at (877) 434-3578 or write to us at Green Dot Customer Service, P.O. Box 1187, Monrovia, California 91017.
